[
		{
			"id" : "0",
			"questionList":[
			{
			"element" : "combo",
			"questionText":"Please select the type of the Cipher",
			"answers":[
				{"value":"Symmetric",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm": "", "operand":"","value":"","operator":""}
				],"nextID" : "1" 
				},
				{"value":"Asymmetric",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm": "", "operand":"","value":"","operator":""}
				],
				"defaultAnswer": true, "nextID" : "1"
				}
			]
			
		},
		{ 	"element" : "combo",
			"questionText":"Please select the type of the symmetric-key algorithm",
			"answers":[
				{"value":"Block",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""},
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}],
				 "nextID" : "2"
				},
				{"value":"Stream",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}
				], "defaultAnswer": true, "nextID" : "2"
			}
			]
		}
		]
		},
		{
			"id" : "1",
			"element" : "combo",
			"questionText":"Please select the type of the symmetric-key algorithm",
			"answers":[
				{"value":"Block",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""},
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}],
				 "nextID" : "2"
				},
				{"value":"Stream",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}
				], "defaultAnswer": true, "nextID" : "2"
			}
			]
		},
		{
			"id" : "2",
			"element" : "text",
			"questionText":"Please enter the name of your algorithm",
			"answers":[
				{"value":"",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""},
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}],
				 "nextID" : "3"
				},
				{"value":"",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}
				], "defaultAnswer": true, "nextID" : "3"
			}
			]
		},
		{
			"id" : "3",
			"element" : "text",
			"questionText":"Please enter the name of the author/company",
			"answers":[
				{"value":"",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""},
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}],
				 "nextID" : "4"
				},
				{"value":"",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}
				], "defaultAnswer": true, "nextID" : "4"
			}
			]
		},
		{
			"id" : "4",
			"element" : "text",
			"questionText":"Please give a short description of your algorithm",
			"answers":[
				{"value":"",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""},
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}],
				 "nextID" : "5"
				},
				{"value":"",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}
				], "defaultAnswer": true, "nextID" : "5"
			}
			]
		},
		{
			"id" : "5",
			"element" : "combo",
			"questionText":"Please select the corresponded key size of your algorithm",
			"answers":[
				{"value":"56",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""},
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}],
				 "nextID" : "6"
				},
				{"value":"128",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}
				], "defaultAnswer": true, "nextID" : "5"
			},
			{"value":"192",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""},
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}],
				 "nextID" : "6"
				},
				{"value":"256",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""},
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}],
				 "nextID" : "6"
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"id" : "6",
			"element" : "text",
			"questionText":"Please enter the block size of the cipher",
			"answers":[
				{"value":"",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""},
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}],
				 "nextID" : "7"
				},
				{"value":"",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}
				], "defaultAnswer": true, "nextID" : "7"
			}
			]
		},
		{
			"id" : "7",
			"element" : "combo",
			"questionText":"Please select the padding used for your algorithm",
			"answers":[
				{"value":"OneAndZeroes Padding",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""},
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}],
				 "nextID" : "8"
				},
				{"value":"Zero Padding", 

				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}
				], "defaultAnswer": true, "nextID" : "8"
			}, 
			{"value":"PKCS7",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""},
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}],
				 "nextID" : "8"
				},
			{"value":"No Padding ",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""},
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}],
				 "nextID" : "8"
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"id" : "8",
			"element" : "checkbox",
			"questionText":"Please select the mode of operation of your algorithm",
			"answers":[
				{"value":"CBC",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""},
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}],
				 "nextID" : "9"
				},
				{"value":"ECB",
				"claferDependencies":[
				{"algorithm":"", "value":"", "operator":""}
				], "defaultAnswer": true, "nextID" : "9"
			}
			]
		}
]